https://www.sffworld.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policysffworld.com does not collect personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. A user’s personally identifying information will not be sold or rented to any other party.sffworld.com users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., name, email address) in the discussion forums or explicitly tells us to do so with submitted information (e.g., book reviews, tv/movie reviews, fiction), that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties.Kids Be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself (your name, address, email address, etc…) to us or anyone else over the Internet.Ad serving We have ads served onto our site by AdSense, Gorilla Nation and ValueClick Media. Please visit their privacy statements.Post Comment Cancel replyComment Name *
Email *
Website
Save my name, email, and website in this browser for the next time I comment.
Sponsors
Your ad here.Contribute to SFFWorldDo you want to contribute and join the SFFWorld Team? More info
Subscribe to email updates
Please leave this field emptyCheck your inbox or spam folder now to confirm your subscription.DISCUSSION FORUM
Recent CommentsLarry on Countdown to Hallowe’en 2020 – Perchance to Dream by Charles BeaumontRandy Money on Countdown to Hallowe’en 2020 – Perchance to Dream by Charles BeaumontLarry on Countdown to Hallowe’en 2020 – Perchance to Dream by Charles BeaumontMike on THE UNSPOKEN NAME by A.K. LarkwoodRandy Money on THE INVISIBLE LIFE OF ADDIE LaRUE by VE SchwabAurora on Arwen Elys Dayton InterviewMark Yon on Archive Review: Bradbury Centenary – Fahrenheit 451David Liss on Archive Review: Bradbury Centenary – Fahrenheit 451Mark Yon on The Living Dead by George A Romero and Daniel KrausJohn Costigan on The Living Dead by George A Romero and Daniel KrausRecent PostsTHE SHATTERED REALM OF ARDOR BENN by Tyler Whitesides (Kingdom of Grit #2)We, Robots: Artificial Intelligence in 100 Stories, Edited by Simon IngsThe Ankh-Morpork Archives Volume 2 by Terry Pratchett and Stephen BriggsTHE THOUSAND DEATHS OF ARDOR BENN by Tyler WhitesidesBone Harvest by James BrogdenBLACK SUN by Rebecca Roanhorse (Between Earth and Sky #1)The Wintertime Paradox by Dave Rudden
